[Music]
all right
hello everyone I've been absent for a
little while because I've been visiting
my Theo and Abuelita in Fajardo in
Puerto Rico it's been a long time since
I've had the chance to travel so far to
see the people I love and speak my
mother tongue the sights and smells were
so different from my home as this is the
land of rain forests and palm trees and
cats and delectable fruit
I'll be dreaming of fresh mangoes for
months
I'm pretty sure I went home as a prune
because I spent most of the trip
swimming but it was incredible to
connect with the nature here knowing
that it held the stories of my ancestors
and appreciating all the hardships and
triumphs that have guided them
throughout the centuries and eventually
led to my own existence it makes me feel
both important and Incredibly small at
the same time
[Music]
it was fascinating to come home to
Washington State where Autumn is
arriving in full force and everything
looks so different it is starting to
feel chilly in the mornings and the
Aspens are turning it is so exciting
[Music]
even though I didn't have much to share
this week in the midst of busyness I did
want to remind everyone watching that
you are loved and wherever you are I'm
sending you a big hug and well wishes
for a new season perhaps this month you
can make it a goal to sit still a little
more often make sure you surround
yourself with people that are respectful
and kind and consider what changes to
your environment might help you thrive
[Music]
foreign
I hope you've had a wonderful wonderful
week I wanted to do a lot this week it
is starting to feel like Autumn it is so
beautiful outside I have so many plans
for Autumn videos but it just just
wasn't gonna happen because
unfortunately I just got back from
Puerto Rico and I'm moving my art
artists Studio from one place to another
and it has been quite the Monumental
task my trip to Puerto Rico was
absolutely wonderful I loved every
moment of it it was so warm it was
definitely a little bit too warm at
times but it was breathtaking and I got
to see El junkie the rainforest and I
got to see my Abuelita in Fajardo and I
just had just such a lovely time talking
with everyone it was so wonderful to
speak my my language and to meet new
people and everyone in Puerto Rico is so
kind and welcoming for the most heart
and it has just been the best and it has
been so lovely to see a lot of family
members that I've not seen for a very
very long time I lived there as a child
and my mommy is a native Puerto Rican
and so it was just so lovely to connect
again with the island my Islands you
know my family's home in the meantime I
appreciate you understanding I I'm not
getting too much done this week but I
appreciate you and I hope to see you
very soon with much more Autumn focused
videos I appreciate your kindness and
patience with me as I am moving things
around finding a new artist studio doing
a whole other bunch of things and I will
see you very soon sending so much love
goodbye
[Music]